Cyrille Bomba

+337.54.25.23.61 • Aix-en-Provence, France • cbngong@gmail.com • www.linkedin.com/in/cyrille-bomba-ngong

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Reliable, energetic and resourceful developer with over three years of experience resolving bug incidents and writing code. Ability to cultivate key client relationships in diverse industries. Expertise in QA testing, web development, DevOps engineering and communication in an agile environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fulll - Aix-en-Provence, France

04/2021 - PRESENT

Junior Frontend Developer

- Developed responsive web applications across platforms using React and TypeScript.
- Worked with a team of 10 developers, architects, tester and PM to resolve front-end issues.
- Created documentation after each pull requests to improve company standards and best practices, shortening the learning time by an average of 16 days.

Atos - Aix-en-Provence, France

10/2019 - 04/2021

Junior DevOps engineer

- Automated server patching for 200+ virtual servers, using Linux, Salt, Jenkins.
- Maintained and troubleshooted production environments.
- Documented maintenance and troubleshooting procedures.
- Provided technical support for QA testers and developers.

Five Guys – *Aix-en-Provence, France*

01/2015 - 07/2018

Manager

- Headed up customer relations, addressed customer needs, worked to resolve any disputes on purchases, and created customer confidence.
- Recruited, trained and led a team of 70 employees, improved team morale by 50% based on anonymous feedback.
- Managed daily operations including scheduling, managing payroll, cash handling, sales forecasting, and deleting tasks as needed. Reconciled cash register 100%.

EDUCATION

ICOGES- Paris, France

Master degree in Corporate Finances, July 2014

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Programming langages: JavaScript, React, TypeScript
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB
- Comfortable working in both Microsoft Windows 10 and Mac OS X.
- Excellent communication skills with a focus on team-building and customer relations.
- Outstanding organizational, multitasking, and problem-solving abilities.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Church of Jesus-Christ of Latter Day Saints – *Aix-en-Provence, France* **Non-Profit Organization**

Since 11/2020

- Bishop of the church.
- Supervised youth and adults activities, services and teachings of the gospel of Jesus-Christ.
- Managed finances in order to help those in need of food, supply, or educational programs.
- Presides in general meetings with others organizations within the church.

CERTIFICATES

M2i – *Aix-en-Provence* 09/2019

DevOps Foundation Certificate - 4 months intensive bootcamp

Webforce3 - Marseille 01/2019

• Certificate of completion in web development – 4 months intensive bootcamp.

LANGUAGE COMPETENCIES

- French: native language
- Italian: fluent (speaking, reading, writing)
- English: fluent (speaking, reading, writing)